=== Plugin Name ===
Contributors: johnkolbert
Donate link: http://www.johnkolbert.com/portfolio/wp-plugins/absolute-privacy
Tags: privacy, registration, moderation
Requires at least: 2.7
Tested up to: 2.7.1
Stable tag: 1.0

Turns your blog into the ultimate private blog: user moderation, blog lock-down, users can chose their own password and must enter their name when registering.

== Description ==

Absolute Privacy turns your WordPress blog into a fully private site where you control who has access. It's perfect for family blogs, private communities, and personal websites.

After activating the plugin your registrations are automatically protected. First, the plugin adds new fields to the registration menu which require the registrant to enter their first and last name, and to choose a password. Newly registered members are given a WordPress role created by the plugin called "Unapproved User" and although they are registered and have a password, they are unable to login until approved.

After registering, the newly registered user is sent an email reminding him/her that they will be unable to login until their account has been approved. The site administrator is sent an email with a link to quickly approve or delete the new user. Once the administrator approves the account the user is sent an email notification. To unapprove a user, simply edit their profile and change their "Role" to "Unapproved User".

A new tab called "Moderate Users" is created in the "Users" area which allows you to quickly view and either approve or delete all unapproved users.

To prevent access to your site for non-logged in viewers, simply navigate to the Absolute Privacy tab under "Settings" and check the "Members Only" box. Your blog now is absolutely private, including RSS feeds.


== Installation ==

Simply upload to your wp-content/plugins folder and activate from the plugins menu. Nothing else to it!

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

Please see the plugins homepage for an up-to-date FAQ.

== Screenshots ==
1. A view of the added registration form fields
2. Custom error for non-approved user trying to login
3. Custom moderation menu to easily approve or delete all unapproved users.
4. Approval is easy: click the link in the approval pending email and press approve

